# Mireya Garza

Houston, TX | 832-679-9585 | mire.garza98@gmail.com

## **Summary**

I have had a lot of community service experience and have grown to excel in many traits. Through these services and experiences, I have gained a lot of patience with customers and children, a very good work ethic, and very good people skills. I believe my work as an instructor and volunteering experience will prove helpful in a team problem-solving environment.

#### Skills

Technical: Photoshop, Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint

**Web Development:** uhclspiritsquad.github.io and katnapper98.github.io **Programming Languages:** Java, Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Languages: Fluent Spanish

## **Work Experience**

Intern Tietronix Software

(January 2018 - June 2018)

• Front-end development

Web application testing

### **Student Mentor**

University of Houston-Clear Lake- Houston, TX

(January 2017 - Present)

- Help students become familiar with topics discussed in class
- Plan and organize workshop events
- Help students become familiar with University resources

#### **Swim instructor**

Lobo Gymnastics- Houston, TX

(June 2016 - August 2016)

- Create lesson plans for different classes
- discipline and keep students engaged in class
- lifeguard duty

## **Volunteer Experience**

## Teal Run Swim Team- Houston, TX

(June 2015 to August 2015)

- Help children with swimming instruction
- Give friendly and instructional attention to various children
- Help out at swim events

## **Houston Humane Society- Houston, TX**

(May 2014 to August 2014)

- Oversaw adoptions and well-being of animals
- Cleaned and fed pens
- Spoke to customers interested in adopting

#### Education

**Bachelor of Science, Computer Science** 

University of Houston-Clear Lake (august 2015 - Present) GPA: 3.378